I think that there's a lot of folks who genuinely want to learn more about the trans world and the
proper ways to interact with the language around trans people, with the politics around trans
people, etc. But sometimes it just feels like there isn't a safe space to do that. And I was
talking to a friend the other day and she was saying her frustration is that, you know, it seems
like cisgendered heterosexual women or just cisgendered women in general end up having to like
be the ones to create those spaces. How come trans folks aren't creating those spaces? And so I had
to tell her, I said, because when you are in the place of privilege, even if it's just a half step
of privilege more than the other, it's on you to carry the burden of creating that space. Now that
was something that she had previously been ignorant to is she wasn't speaking out of transphobia. She
was speaking out of ignorance to really what the, um, I'm sure there's like a really fancy word for
this, but I'm just going to say this, like the hierarchical dynamics of restorative justice are
that girl went to college.